hollywoodgrind.com 2011-03-20

# Hollywood Grind Privacy Policy

**Hollywood Grind Privacy Policy – Last Updated February, 2009**

Thank you for visiting Hollywood Grind ("we" or "us") Web site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the collection and use of the personal information you submit on Web pages where this policy is posted.

As we operate internationally, and many of our computer systems are currently based in the United States, your personal data will be processed by us in the U.S. where data protection and privacy regulations may not offer the same level of protection as in other parts of the world, such as the European Union. If you create a user account with this site as a visitor from outside the United States, you will be asked during the initial registration to consent to the collection and/or processing in the United States of your personally identifiable information, which includes the use of cookies as described below.

**The Information We Collect**

At Hollywood Grind you can vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, e-mail address, and IP address.

**How We Use The Information**

We currently only use the information provided to make your comments visible on the site. All other information is stored on our servers to identify information you gave us in filling out our forms, or by visiting our site, and is used internally only for statistics. Hollywood Grind does not, and will not, sell, or distribute, any information obtained.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

Agents and contractors of Hollywood Grind who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Hollywood Grind.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.

**Collection of Information by Third Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites’ privacy policies, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

At times reputable third parties may present or serve the advertisements on Hollywood Grind. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party ad server may collect from you.

**Cookies and Other Technical Information**

We send "cookies" to your computer primarily to enhance your online experience. "Cookies" are files that can identify you as a unique customer, or visitor, and store your personal preferences as well as technical information (including click through and click stream data). Cookies can either be permanent (i.e., they remain on your computer until you delete them) or temporary (i.e., they last only until you close your browser). We may also use "Web beacons" that monitor your use of our sites. Web beacons (or Web bugs) are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a Web page for the purpose of transferring data, such as the IP (Internet Protocol) address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the Web beacon appears, the URL (Uniform Resource Locator) of the page on which the Web beacon appears, the time the page containing the Web beacon was viewed, the types of browser that fetched the Web beacon and the identification number of any cookie on the computer previously placed by that server. When corresponding with you via HTML capable e-mail, Web beacons let us know whether you received and opened our e-mail.

If you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information can be stored in or linked to other data stored in the cookies/Web beacons.

By accepting this Privacy Policy, you specifically agree to our use of cookies and Web beacons as described herein. You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Additionally, by setting your Web browser to display HTML e-mails as text only, you may be able to prevent the use of some Web beacons. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, certain areas of our sites can only be accessed in conjunction with cookies or similar devices and you should be aware that disabling cookies or similar devices might prevent you from accessing some of our content, and features the site may provide.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

At this time no one except our administrative staff can access any information collected about you.

**Children’s Privacy**

Hollywood Grind offers the ability for readers to comment. The comment form asks only for a nickname and email address. No personally identifiable information is colllected.

**Notification Regarding Updates**

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.
